

### **Profile Info**

I am a highly motivated Junior Software Developer with a strong passion for programming, technology and with 2.5 years in IT environment.

I am excited to bring my skills and enthusiasm to a dynamic software development team and make a meaningful contribution to the success of the company.

### **Technical skills**

- Javascript
- React
- Neact
- Node
- Express
- MongoDb
- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- React-
- React
- Material-UI,
  Sccs

bootstrap

### Soft skills

- Problem-solving skills and critical thinking.
- Communication skills
- People and interpersonal skills
- Self-awareness
- Self-learning
- Accountability
- Time management.

### Languages

- English Advanced
- German Elementary

# Neretljak Esmir

### Software Developer

Phone

**Email** 

esmirneretljak@gmail.com

**Address** 

Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

#### Linkedin

(+387) 062/927-323

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ esmir-neretljak/

#### Github

https://github.com/Esmir-dev

## **Experience**

#### Data Specialist

Checklens I Sarajevo

- Testing AI models
- Training AI models
- · Proactively participated in meetings and helped create new practices

# Data Analyst

Nov 2019 - Jun 2020

Jul 2020 - Apr 2022

- PixIbrain | Sarajevo
- Collection data for products
- Worked with AI software for food market
- Collection and manipulation with data

#### Student Jobs - External Contractor

Jul 2015 - Oct 2019

Work & Travel Experience Ocean City (United States of America)

• Worked in various positions in the field of tourism

DHL Germany Hamburg (Germany)

• Sorted and distributed mail, packages and letters

SHW AG & Georg Fischer Tuttlingen & Singen (Germany)

- Production Of Brake Discs For Cars (BMW, Audi, Porsche, Passat..)
- Production Of Autoparts, control and work on assembly line

BMW Munchen (Germany)

• Assistance to permanent employees

### **Education**

### Paragon (IT Program for full stack developer) 2021 - 2022 Mistral Sarajevo, Bosnia and Herzegovina

- Program for full stack developers, which lasted 11 months where main focus and work was with MERN stack.
- Won the coding challenge, with an application for the digitization of the health system of Canton Sarajevo, together with three other members of my team.

#### Bachelor's & Master's degree

2014 - 2020

Faculty of Science/ University of Sarajevo -Regional and Spatial planning

• Sustainable development of the development of a certain area, and environmental protection.